<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Areasofpractices on SHL and Associates</title>
    <link>/areasofpractice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Areasofpractices on SHL and Associates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/areasofpractice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/commercial-litigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/commercial-litigation/</guid>
      <description> Commercial Litigation At SHL &amp;amp; Associates Lawyers, our highly experienced and dedicated team of commercial litigation lawyers provide clear, honest and realistic advice to our clients in any commercial dispute.
From informal settlement mediation or conferences to formal arbitration and contested court hearings, our experienced lawyers have a proven track record of providing strategic advice to maximise our clients’ chance of success.
Areas of expertise
 Contractual disputes Corporations Act litigation Directors’ duties Derivative proceedings Shareholder disputes Shareholder oppression claims Injunctions Freezing orders Specific performance Rectification Rescission Constructive trusts Defamation Property and leasing Disputes Trust sale pursuant to section - 66G applications Statutory demands Building and construction - litigation Class actions Trade practices Debt recovery Insolvency and bankruptcy Professional negligence claim Workplace disputes Succession and contested wills Matrimonial and custody - disputes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/commercial-property-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/commercial-property-law/</guid>
      <description>Commercial and Corporate Law SHL &amp;amp; Associates Lawyers provide an extensive range of corporate and commercial legal advice and services. By leveraging our business insights and proven legal knowledge and expertise, we are well-placed to advise you on all major business and commercial transactions and commercial decisions.
Areas of Expertise
-Purchases &amp;amp; sales of businesses -Commercial contract review and preparation -Corporate structure advisory. -Business establishment and company incorporation -Establishment of trust (including unit and discretionary trusts) -Shareholder agreements -Purchase and sale of shares -Corporate governance &amp;amp; compliance -Directors duties -Corporations Act 2001 advisory -Franchising and licensing -Shareholder disputes -Advise on Foreign Investment Review Board (&amp;rdquo;FIRB&amp;rdquo;) applications -Joint ventures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/criminal-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/criminal-law/</guid>
      <description>Criminal Law We represent clients in all categories of offences, including assault offences, AVOs, traffic offences, firearms &amp;amp; weapons offences, larceny, drug charges, sexual assault, and fraud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/family-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/family-law/</guid>
      <description>Family Law We understand that relationship breakdowns can be a traumatic and uncertain time. At SHL &amp;amp; Associates Lawyers, our extensive experience is what you need in dealing with difficult and often emotional family or matrimonial disputes. Whether it is mediation, roundtable conference or formal legal proceeding, we are committed to provide you with tailored and professional legal advice to help you achieve closure.
Areas of Expertise
-Binding financial agreements -Divorce &amp;amp; separation -Parenting issues -Property and financial settlements -De-facto relationships -Child support -Spouse maintenance -Location order -Recovery application -Relocation and travel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/immigration-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/immigration-services/</guid>
      <description>Immigration Service At SHL &amp;amp; Associates Lawyers, we assist our clients in all areas related to migrating to Australia. We provide tailored advice based on the most up to date immigration decisions and legislative framework. Our objective is to serve our client’s needs, assessing their situation, clearly explaining the options available to them and advising our clients on the best solution based on their unique circumstances.
Our immigration legal services assist clients with a wide range of visa and migration legal queries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/notary-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/notary-public/</guid>
      <description> Notary Public When you need to serve a document in an overseas jurisdiction, our principal lawyer, Mr. Jonathan Lu, is a duly qualified and appointed Public Notary who can assist with all of your notarisation requirements.
Mr. Jonathan Lu provides the following notary services:
 Authenticating documents and information for overseas use Witnessing signatures of individuals to documents and authenticating identity Preparing and witnessing powers of attorney for use overseas Certifying true copies of documents for overseas use Witnessing and authenticating the status of companies, businesses and commercial transactions Dealing with documentation for land, property and deceased estates overseas  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/areasofpractice/property-law-conveyancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/areasofpractice/property-law-conveyancing/</guid>
      <description>Property Law &amp;amp; Conveyancing SHL &amp;amp; Associates Lawyers’ property and conveyancing team has extensive experience in all aspects of property law. Our specialist lawyers work closely and collaboratively with clients providing the most practical commercial advice specifically tailored to their expectations and needs.
Areas of Expertise
-Purchase &amp;amp; sale of properties -Off-the-plan purchases and sales -Contract review &amp;amp; preparation -Commercial agreements -Property development -Property related advisory (taxation, ownership, finance) -Foreign investment -Commercial and retail leasing -Mortgages &amp;amp; securities -Strata disputes -Subdivisions -Construction contracts -Discretionary and unit trust -Joint Ventures -Tenancy disputes -Property transfer -Valuations -Stamp duty and taxes -Property litigation -Foreign Investment and Review Board (&amp;rdquo;FIRB&amp;rdquo;) applications</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>